In England they have the Labour Party. It's a party for the laborers. It ideally works on behalf
of making sure that legislation regards the laborers who are the majority of the country.
For everyone who has been coming in my DMs like, well actually, actually it's more like, well
actually, please listen to the words that I have said in the video. I'm gonna play one more time.
In England they have the Labour Party. It ideally works on behalf of making sure that legislation
regards the laborers who are the majority of the country. I am thoughtful in how I speak, so please
be thoughtful in how you listen. The reason why it's imperative that I said the word ideally,
wow a lot of cheese in my teeth, is because that's what it's supposed to do. Currently that is not what
it's doing. However, there is something to be said for the fact that it even exists with the capability
to do that. Something that here in the States we do not have. Which was my actual point.
But I'm fine.